https://www.enzolifesciences.com/footer/privacy/

Online Purchasing Account
You are logged on as Guest.
LoginRegister a New AccountShopping cart (Empty)
Change country
ProductsTechnology PlatformsCell BiologyGenomicsImmunoassays & Biochemical AssaysImmunohistochemistrySmall Molecule ChemistryPromotions & SpecialsMarketsAnimal CareBioprocessCoronavirusCytogeneticsPathologyPersonal CareVaccinesApplied ScienceCancerDrug DiscoveryEpigeneticsImmunologyImmuno-OncologyMetabolismNeurosciencePredictive ToxicologyProteostasisBrowse ProductsAlphabetically [A-Z]By Product TypeAntibodiesAssays and KitsBiochemicalsDyes / LabelsInstrumentsNucleic AcidPeptidesProteinsWestern BlotNew ProductsQuick LinksCertificates of AnalysisELISA kits Search ToolAntibody Search ToolApoptosis Detection GuideFlow Cytometry
Spectra ViewerFlying Start New Lab ProgramCustomized Solutions For Your WorkflowPromotions & SpecialsScience CenterScientific LiteratureApplication NotesE-BooksFlyersBrochuresCatalogsScientific PostersAll Scientific LiteratureTechNotesHow to Differentiate Between Cell Death Types?NGS Workflow and Fundamentals of Sample PreparationWhat is PEGylation and why is it an Important Process?How Do Histone Modifications Regulate Gene Expression?Are Sample Extraction Methods Necessary For ELISA?IHC Counterstains for Enzyme/Chromogen and Fluorescent ImmunostainingWhat Controls are Necessary for Immunohistochemistry?What is Next Generation Sequencing (NGS)?All TechNotesInterestingWebinarsCollaborations at WorkIHC Hall of FameConference CalendarPromotions & Special OffersSocial MediaFacebookLinkedInTwitterInstagramJoin Us!Support
About UsCorporate ProfileCollaborations at WorkPress ReleasesCareersTrade Shows & ConferencesContact UsTechnical SupportWorldwide Distributors
Home » footer » Privacy
Privacy Policy
To the attention of all EU customers: We have updated our website privacy policy to reflect changes associated with GDPR.
Enzo Life Sciences, Inc. (“ELS”) respects individual privacy and values the confidence of its customers, partners, investors and employees. This Privacy Policy sets forth ELS’s practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that you may provide through this site. Please read this entire privacy policy before using this site or submitting information to Enzo through this site.
DATA COLLECTION: Enzo only collects personally identifiable data such as your name, address, telephone number and email address when you voluntarily submit it to ELS. This information may be used by Enzo personnel as a means to contact you to obtain more information, to improve this site, or it might be used to provide you with information that you have requested or additional information which Enzo believes may be of interest to you. The data will not be transferred outside ELS without your prior consent, but may be used within Enzo or by a company acting as an agent of Enzo for processing and mailing purposes. Enzo may also use this information within the company for performing marketing studies or for other commercial purposes for which it may receive compensation.ELS maintains the data collected in an electronic database of voluntarily submitted personally identifiable information. Enzo and its agents may exchange such information with each other or with you over the internet or intranet systems for the purposes of carrying out the services described above.While ELS makes every reasonable effort to protect the information collected through its websites, please be aware that there is always some risk involved when submitting data over the Internet. We cannot guarantee that our website is 100% safe from illegal tampering or “hacking.’ Any data transmitted over the Internet may be at risk; however, once it is received at Enzo and entered into its database, it has the same protection that Enzo extends to its own confidential information.ELS tracks the total number of visitors to our website, the number of visitors to each page of the website, and the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers. No personally identifiable information is gathered in this process.The ELS web server software automatically collects a variety of information (as is standard for most software of this kind). This information does not include any personal data. Data collected include your IP-address, pages you visit during your stay on the ELS website, type of browser, operating system and screen resolution you are using. This information is not personally identifiable, but will help us to improve and fine-tune our website. This information is stored in log files and is used solely for statistical purposes and not combined with your personally identifiable information.
UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION:If at any time you wish to stop receiving emails or other communications from us, or if you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would like to have that information deleted from our records, please notify us. You may also request access to personal data about you that ELS holds and you may have the opportunity to request a correction or amendment to your personal data. As a reminder to you when exchanging emails, any email that you send or receive on your employer’s email system may be the property of your employer. Consequently, your employer has the ability to review your personal information sent via email.
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES:As a convenience to our visitors, our sites currently contain links to a number of other (non-ELS) sites that we believe may offer useful information. The privacy policy presented here does not apply to those sites. You should contact these sites directly for information on their privacy policies, confidentiality agreements and data collection/distribution procedures.
CHILDREN’S POLICY:The ELS website is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is a child under the age of 13.
COOKIES:Please refer to our Cookie policy.
PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES:Any changes to the Enzo Internet privacy policy will be posted on this page. This privacy policy was last updated: February 01 2009.
Recommend this page
Tweet
another CS2 website
Keep in touch
©2020 Enzo Life Sciences, Inc.,PrivacyDisclaimerTermsLegalSitemapFeedback
